

System and network administrator

- 06.61.37.14.15
- alexandre.malescot@pm.me
- Montrouge/92120/France
- LinkedIn:
 alexandre-malescot-470949172
- Portfolio and CV:
 https://portfolio.itmader.ovh

PERSONAL INFORMATIONS

I am 29 years old and I am passionate about IT.

My exam to become a systems and network administrator is in September 2021!

I would like to continue my studies in the field of cybersecurity (BAC +5).

I have a driving licence A and B and I have a car.

SKILLS

7 / 10

Linux

8 / 10

Network

9 / 10

Rigorous

10 / 10

Passionate

6 / 10

Windows

DEGREES

ASRC - Systems, Networks and Cloud Administrator - BAC +4 ASTON SQLI GROUP

2019 - 2021

TSRS - System, Network and Security

Technician - BAC +2

ASTON SQLI GROUP

2018 - 2019

MMIR - Microcomputer and Network

Maintainer - BAC

ASTON SQLI GROUP

2017 - 2018

EXPÉRIENCES

Administrator / Support level 3

Luceor/Velizy-Villacoublay/in progress

- Pre-sales & PS assistance
- Training of our partners
- Production assistance
- Luceor internal office support
- Support for the entire after-sales service chain

Support technician level 3

Luceor/Velizy-Villacoublay/2018-2019

- Development of support tools
- Implementation of test platforms
- Administration of the company's internal computer system
- Management of the after-sales service

Technician level 2

Bouygues Construction/Guyancourt/2018-2018

- Treatment of hardware and software incidents.
- DELL hardware after-sales service
- Deployment of masters
- Use of AD and SCCM consoles
- Asset management (new users, mobile computers)
- User data management and confidentiality
- User relations (advice and best practices)
- Management of incident and request backlogs